{
    "subject": "Norodom_Sihanouk",
    "predicate": "created",
    "object": "My_Village_at_Sunset",
    "human_readable": "Norodom Sihanouk created the film My Village at Sunset.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9141978025436401,
            "question": "Who created the film 'My Village at Sunset'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8718198537826538,
            "question": "What is the title of the film created by Norodom Sihanouk?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7571554183959961,
            "question": "What is the name of the film about a village at sunset?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6723573803901672,
            "question": "Who is the director behind the film 'My Village at Sunset'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6426459550857544,
            "question": "Name a film directed by Norodom Sihanouk."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6345311403274536,
            "question": "What type of work did Norodom Sihanouk create?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5845180153846741,
            "question": "Is 'My Village at Sunset' a fictional or non-fictional film?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4877643287181854,
            "question": "Can you think of other films with similar themes to 'My Village at Sunset'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.36579886078834534,
            "question": "Norodom Sihanouk worked in which field based on the given information?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.19218763709068298,
            "question": "What can you infer about Norodom Sihanouk's interests based on his work?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Norodom Sihanouk created the film My Village at Sunset.",
            "html": "yago_21814_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Norodom Sihanouk worked in which field based on the given information?",
            "html": "yago_21814_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you think of other films with similar themes to 'My Village at Sunset'?",
            "html": "yago_21814_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is 'My Village at Sunset' a fictional or non-fictional film?",
            "html": "yago_21814_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_21814_102.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_21814_119.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_21814_120.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_21814_133.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_21814_160.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_21814_23.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_21814_29.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_21814_30.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_21814_57.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_21814_7.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe documents clearly state that Norodom Sihanouk directed and produced the film \"My Village at Sunset\" in 1992. Therefore, the triple \"Norodom Sihanouk created the film My Village at Sunset\" is supported by the information provided."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        }
    },
    "final_decision": "true",
    "actual_decision": "true",
    "analysis": {
        "error_category": "caafscd",
        "error_detail": "cdscsd",
        "category": "csdcs",
        "stratum": "fwefew",
        "topic": "wefw"
    }
}